**FREE SHIPPING** on US orders $49.99+

Fox Switches are now available! [**Shop Now**](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/en-uk/products/glorious-fox-linear-switches "Fox Linear Switches")

{ "settings": {"nav\_top\_category\_title":"Shop","nav\_top\_cateogry\_url":null,"text\_color":"pale-black","show\_nav\_footer\_utils":true}, "nav\_top\_category\_handle": "shop", "blocks": \[{ "type":"link\_list", "settings":{"title":"Keyboards","links":"keyboards"} , "title\_handle":"keyboards","links": \[{ "title":"GMMK PRO", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/gmmk-pro", "title\_handle":"gmmk-pro"},{ "title":"GMMK 2", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/gmmk-2", "title\_handle":"gmmk-2"},{ "title":"GMMK Numpad", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/gmmk-numpad-keyboard", "title\_handle":"gmmk-numpad"},{ "title":"Barebones Keyboards", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/barebones-keyboards", "title\_handle":"barebones-keyboards"},{ "title":"Prebuilt Keyboards", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/prebuilt-keyboards", "title\_handle":"prebuilt-keyboards"},{ "title":"Keyboard Accessories", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/keyboard-accessories", "title\_handle":"keyboard-accessories"},{ "title":"View All", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/keyboards", "title\_handle":"view-all"},{ "title":"Compare Keyboards", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/compare-glorious-keyboards", "title\_handle":"compare-keyboards"}\]},{ "type":"link\_list", "settings":{"title":"Mice","links":"mice"} , "title\_handle":"mice","links": \[{ "title":"PRO Mice", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/pro-series-mice", "title\_handle":"pro-mice"},{ "title":"V2 Mice", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/v2-mice", "title\_handle":"v2-mice"},{ "title":"Model O", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/model-o-mice", "title\_handle":"model-o"},{ "title":"Model D", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/model-d-mice", "title\_handle":"model-d"},{ "title":"Model I", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/model-i-mice", "title\_handle":"model-i"},{ "title":"Wireless Mice", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/wireless-mice", "title\_handle":"wireless-mice"},{ "title":"Wired Mice", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/wired-mice", "title\_handle":"wired-mice"},{ "title":"Mini Mice", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/mini-mice", "title\_handle":"mini-mice"},{ "title":"Mice Accessories", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/mice-accessories", "title\_handle":"mice-accessories"},{ "title":"View All", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/mice", "title\_handle":"view-all"},{ "title":"Compare Mice", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/compare-glorious-mice", "title\_handle":"compare-mice"}\]},{ "type":"link\_list", "settings":{"title":"Keycaps","links":"keycaps"} , "title\_handle":"keycaps","links": \[{ "title":"KeyCapsules", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/keycapsules", "title\_handle":"keycapsules"},{ "title":"GPBT Gradient Series", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/gpbt-gradient-series", "title\_handle":"gpbt-gradient-series"},{ "title":"Grapefruit", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/gpbt-pink-grapefruit-keycaps", "title\_handle":"grapefruit"},{ "title":"Celestial", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/gpbt-celestial-series-keycaps", "title\_handle":"celestial"},{ "title":"Polychroma", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/glorious-polychroma-keycaps", "title\_handle":"polychroma"},{ "title":"Aura V2", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/glorious-aura-keycaps-v2-black", "title\_handle":"aura-v2"},{ "title":"ABS Doubleshot", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/gmmk-keycaps", "title\_handle":"abs-doubleshot"},{ "title":"View All", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/keycaps", "title\_handle":"view-all"}\]},{ "type":"link\_list", "settings":{"title":"Switches","links":"switches"} , "title\_handle":"switches","links": \[{ "title":"Fox Linear Switches", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/glorious-fox-linear-switches", "title\_handle":"fox-linear-switches"},{ "title":"Panda Tactile Switches", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/glorious-panda-mechanical-switches", "title\_handle":"panda-tactile-switches"},{ "title":"Lynx Linear Switches", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/glorious-mechanical-switches-lynx", "title\_handle":"lynx-linear-switches"},{ "title":"Raptor Clicky Switches", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/glorious-raptor-switches", "title\_handle":"raptor-clicky-switches"},{ "title":"View All", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/switches", "title\_handle":"view-all"}\]},{ "type":"link\_list", "settings":{"title":"Mousepads","links":"mousepads"} , "title\_handle":"mousepads","links": \[{ "title":"Large 11 x 13", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/large-stitched-cloth-mousepad", "title\_handle":"large-11-x-13"},{ "title":"Large Extended 11 x 36", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/black-stitched-cloth-mousepad", "title\_handle":"large-extended-11-x-36"},{ "title":"XL Heavy 16 x 18", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/white-stitched-cloth-mousepad", "title\_handle":"xl-heavy-16-x-18"},{ "title":"XL Slim 16 x 18", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/stitched-cloth-mousepad-xl-16-x-18-slim", "title\_handle":"xl-slim-16-x-18"},{ "title":"XL Extended 14 x 24", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/stitched-cloth-mousepad-xl-extended", "title\_handle":"xl-extended-14-x-24"},{ "title":"XXL Extended 18 x 36", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/stitched-cloth-mousepad-xxl-extended-18-x-36", "title\_handle":"xxl-extended-18-x-36"},{ "title":"3XL Extended 24 x 48", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/stitched-cloth-mousepad-xxxl-extended-24x-48", "title\_handle":"3xl-extended-24-x-48"},{ "title":"View All", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/mousepads", "title\_handle":"view-all"}\]},{ "type":"link\_list", "settings":{"title":"Accessories","links":"accessories"} , "title\_handle":"accessories","links": \[{ "title":"Mice Accessories", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/mice-accessories", "title\_handle":"mice-accessories"},{ "title":"Keyboard Accessories", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/keyboard-accessories", "title\_handle":"keyboard-accessories"},{ "title":"GMMK PRO Accessories", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/gmmk-pro-accessories", "title\_handle":"gmmk-pro-accessories"},{ "title":"GMMK 2 Accessories", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/gmmk-2-accessories", "title\_handle":"gmmk-2-accessories"},{ "title":"Numpad Acessories", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/numpad-accessories", "title\_handle":"numpad-acessories"},{ "title":"Wrist Rests", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/wrist-rests", "title\_handle":"wrist-rests"},{ "title":"Trident Headset Holder", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/trident-headset-holder", "title\_handle":"trident-headset-holder"},{ "title":"View All", "url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/accessories", "title\_handle":"view-all"}\]},{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"PRO Series","link":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/pro-series"} ,"link\_handle": "pro-series" },{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"Gift Cards","link":"\\/en-uk\\/products\\/gift-card"} ,"link\_handle": "gift-cards" },{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"Shop All","link":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/shop-all"} ,"link\_handle": "shop-all" },{ "type":"divider", "settings":{} },{ "type":"image\_link", "settings":{"image":"\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/cdn\\/shop\\/files\\/Nav\_Feature\_Image\_-\_Fox\_Switch.webp?v=1721669225","text":"Glorious Fox Switches are here!","url":null} ,"image\_data": { "src":"\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/cdn\\/shop\\/files\\/Nav\_Feature\_Image\_-\_Fox\_Switch.webp?v=1721669225", "alt":"Fox Switch is available now", "width":562, "height":316} , "link\_handle":"glorious-fox-switches-are-here" }\] }

{ "settings": {"nav\_top\_category\_title":"Build","nav\_top\_cateogry\_url":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/guided-purchasing","text\_color":"pale-black","show\_nav\_footer\_utils":false}, "nav\_top\_category\_handle": "build", "blocks": \[\] }

{ "settings": {"nav\_top\_category\_title":"Learn","nav\_top\_cateogry\_url":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/learn","text\_color":"pale-black","show\_nav\_footer\_utils":true}, "nav\_top\_category\_handle": "learn", "blocks": \[{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"Getting Started","link":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/getting-started"} ,"link\_handle": "getting-started" },{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"Glorious Features","link":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/glorious-features"} ,"link\_handle": "glorious-features" },{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"Perks","link":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/why-buy-dtc"} ,"link\_handle": "perks" },{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"All Topics","link":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/learn"} ,"link\_handle": "all-topics" },{ "type":"divider", "settings":{} },{ "type":"image\_link", "settings":{"image":"\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/cdn\\/shop\\/files\\/GPBTKabuto\_Web\_NavFeature.webp?v=1719851807","text":"Missed Kabuto? Don’t Miss the Next Limited-Release Drop in August","url":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/keycapsules"} ,"image\_data": { "src":"\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/cdn\\/shop\\/files\\/GPBTKabuto\_Web\_NavFeature.webp?v=1719851807", "alt":"Close up of GPBT Kabuto novelty keys featuring samurai masks", "width":562, "height":316} , "link\_handle":"missed-kabuto-don-t-miss-the-next-limited-release-drop-in-august" }\] }

{ "settings": {"nav\_top\_category\_title":"Software","nav\_top\_cateogry\_url":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/software","text\_color":"pale-black","show\_nav\_footer\_utils":false}, "nav\_top\_category\_handle": "software", "blocks": \[\] }

{ "settings": {"nav\_top\_category\_title":"Support","nav\_top\_cateogry\_url":null,"text\_color":"pale-black","show\_nav\_footer\_utils":true}, "nav\_top\_category\_handle": "support", "blocks": \[{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"Order Support","link":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/support"} ,"link\_handle": "order-support" },{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"Product Guides","link":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/product-guides"} ,"link\_handle": "product-guides" },{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"How-To Articles","link":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/support-viewall-howto"} ,"link\_handle": "how-to-articles" },{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"Product Registration","link":"https:\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/tools\\/product-registration"} ,"link\_handle": "product-registration" },{ "type":"link", "settings":{"title":"Contact Us","link":"\\/en-uk\\/pages\\/contact"} ,"link\_handle": "contact-us" }\] }

{ "settings": {}, "blocks": \[\] }

{ "settings": {"footer\_title":"\\u003cp\\u003e\\u003cstrong\\u003eNeed help?\\u003c\\/strong\\u003e We're available 24\\/7\\u003c\\/p\\u003e","show\_live\_chat\_cta":true,"live\_chat\_cta\_text":"Live Chat","live\_chat\_cta\_icon":"\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/cdn\\/shop\\/files\\/UI\_Icons.svg?v=1705772547","show\_email\_cta":true,"email\_cta\_text":"Email","email\_cta\_url":"https:\\/\\/contact.gorgias.help\\/forms\\/k77oyz80","email\_cta\_icon":"\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/cdn\\/shop\\/files\\/UI\_Icons\_52020147-8f75-432a-b5a6-f8f177f8b473.svg?v=1714640579"}}

{ "settings": {"search\_placeholder":"Search Glorious","bg\_color":"#ffffff","navigation\_menu":"popular-searches","category\_1\_name":"Mice","category\_1\_url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/mice","category\_1\_image":"\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/cdn\\/shop\\/files\\/Mice\_collection.webp?v=1714640619","category\_2\_name":"Keyboards","category\_2\_url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/keyboards","category\_2\_image":"\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/cdn\\/shop\\/files\\/Keyboards\_collection.webp?v=1714640619","category\_3\_name":"Keycaps","category\_3\_url":"\\/en-uk\\/collections\\/keycaps","category\_3\_image":"\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/cdn\\/shop\\/files\\/Keycaps\_collection.webp?v=1714640619","category\_nav\_icon":"\\/\\/www.gloriousgaming.com\\/cdn\\/shop\\/files\\/Icon\_Arrow\_Forward\_Function\_Navigation.svg?v=1714640618"}}

clear

Popular Searches

Popular Categories

[](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/en-uk/collections/mice)[Mice

](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/en-uk/collections/mice)

[](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/en-uk/collections/keyboards)[Keyboards

](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/en-uk/collections/keyboards)

[](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/en-uk/collections/keycaps)[Keycaps

](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/en-uk/collections/keycaps)

Privacy Policy
==============

Understand how Glorious Gaming protects your privacy. Our comprehensive Privacy Policy explains data collection, usage, and security measures to ensure your information is safe. Review our policies to stay informed.

Introduction
------------

Glorious LLC (**“Glorious”** or **“We”**) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy (the **“Privacy Policy”**).

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit our websites [www.gloriousgaming.com](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/ "https://www.gloriousgaming.com/") and  
[www.gloriousforum.com](https://gloriousforum.com/ "https://gloriousforum.com/") (collectively, our “**Website**”) or communicate with us through email, text, and other electronic messaging, and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time as described below. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

Children Under the Age of 16
----------------------------

Our Website is not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on this Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or username you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It
------------------------------------------------------

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website depending on how you interact with us and what products or services you use._**  
  
Information You Provide to Us**_

If you fill out a form on our Website that requires contact information, such as signing up for a newsletter, submitting a request for information, or purchasing products and services, we will collect and process that information to provide you with the communication, products, or services.  These types of personal information may include your name, email address, company name, job title, your postal address, and payment and billing information. We use this information solely to process payments and deliver the products and services you requested.  
  
You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk.  
  
_**Information We Automatically Collect Through Cookies or Similar Technologies**_

When you use our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies (e.g., cookies or similar technologies) to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

* Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data and logs of the resources that you access and use on the Website.
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.  

The information we collect automatically may include personal information. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
* Speed up your searches.
* Recognize you when you return to our Website.  

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
* **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Website and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit Glorious, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

_**  
Personal Information Collected When You Use Our Products or Services**_

When you use our products and services, we collect other  
types of personal information.  These types of personal information include:

* Username
* IP Address
* Name
* Email address
* Shipping and Billing Address(es)
* Telephone Number
* Order History

We may also collect usage data regarding your use of our products and services and this data may contain personal information.

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

* To present our Website and its contents to you.
* To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
* To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it.
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
* For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to email you about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or unsubscribe from the corresponding email type using the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of one such email.

We do not sell personal information to third parties (pursuant to California Civil Code Sections 1798.100-1798.99, also known as the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018).

The Legal Bases for Collecting and Processing Information
---------------------------------------------------------

We use the following legal bases for collecting personal information:

* We may collect or process information with tyour consent, such as when you subscribe to our newsletter, ask for information, or purchase products or services.
* We may collect or process information we need to provide our products or services or fulfill a contractual obligation.
* We may collect or process information to fulfill a legal obligation.
* We may collect information when we have a legitimate interest to do so, such as for marketing, as long as our legitimate interests are not outweighed by your rights.
* We may collect or process information if necessary to protect the vital interests of the user or another individual.

How Long We Retain Your Information
-----------------------------------

We retain your personal information for as long as it is needed to provide our services to you and to fulfill our legal obligations and for a reasonable period of time after such services are completed.

Disclosure of Your Information
------------------------------

We may disclose aggregated information about our suers, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:

* To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Glorious, LLC's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Glorious, LLC about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an email address to use a "refer a friend" feature of our Website, we will transmit the contents of that email and your email address to the recipients.
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
* With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
* To enforce or apply our [Terms of Service and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/pages/terms-of-service "https://www.gloriousgaming.com/pages/terms-of-service")
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Glorious, LLC, our customers, or others.

Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information
------------------------------------------------------

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

* **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some  
    browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
* **Promotional Offers from Glorious.** If you do not wish to have your email address  
    used by Glorious to promote our products or services, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or by unsubscribing from the corresponding email type using the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of one such email.

Accessing and Correcting Your Information
-----------------------------------------

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User  
Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have  
been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our [Terms of Service](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/pages/terms-of-service "https://www.gloriousgaming.com/pages/terms-of-service").

Your State Privacy Rights
-------------------------

State consumer privacy laws may provide their residents with additional rights regarding our use of their personal information.

California, Colorado, Connecticut, Delaware, Florida, Indiana, Iowa, Montana, Oregon, Tennessee, Texas, Utah, and Virginia provide (now or in the future) their state residents with rights to:

* Confirm whether we process their personal information.
* Access and delete certain personal information.
* Correct inaccuracies in their personal information, taking into account the information's nature processing purose (excluding Iowa and Utah).
* Data portability.
* Opt-out of personal data processing for:
* targeted advertising (excluding Iowa):
* sales; or
* profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects (excluding Iowa and Utah).
* Either limit (opt-out of) or require consent to process sensitive personal data.

The exact scope of these rights may vary by state. To exercise any of these rights, or to appeal a decision regarding a consumer rights request, please email [\[email protected\]](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Nevada provides its residents with a limited right to opt-out of certain personal information sales. However, please know we do not currently sell data triggering that statute's opt-out requirements.

EU / EEA Rights Regarding Access to and Control Over Personal Information
-------------------------------------------------------------------------

If you reside in the EU/EEA, you may have the following rights with regard to your personal information:

* Right of information and access - You have the right to access your personal information we have about you and to be provided with a copy of your personal information.
* Right to rectification - You have the right to correct or update your inaccurate or out of date personal information.
* Right of erasure - You have the right to request that your personal information be permanently erased/deleted.
* Right to restrict processing - You have the right to restrict the processing of your personal information.
* Right to object to processing - You have the right to object to specific types of processing of your personal information.
* Right to portability - You may ask to receive a portable copy of your personal information in a format that may be transferred to another organization.
* Right not to be subject to decisions based soley on Automated Decision Making - You have the right not to be subject to decisions based solely on automated processing.
* Right to complain to a data protection authority - You have the right to complain to a supervisory autority in the country in which you reside.
* Right to withdraw consent - I f you have given us consent to collect or process your personal information, you may withdraw that consent at any time.
* The Right to Non-Discrimination - We may not discriminate against you if you exercise your privacy rights.

If you wish to exercise any of these rights please submit a request to [\[email protected\]](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

We may charge a reasonable fee if your request is not valid under applicable law, repetitive or excessive.  We may also request additional information from you in order to verify  
your identity before processing your request.

Personal Information may be transferred from users residing in the European Union to our servers, partners, or vendors located in the United States and other non-EU countries where there may not be an adequacy opinion issued with respect to that country. We have taken appropriate safeguards to ensure that Personal Information remains protected wherever it is transferred. 

Data Security
-------------

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted during transmission and at rest in our or our designated service providers’ data centers.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure.  
Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address specified in your account and/or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

Contact Information
-------------------

To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.gloriousgaming.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### Let’s Keep in Touch

Sign up for exclusive deals, new arrivals, and more.

#### About

#### About

#### Help

#### Help

#### Community

#### Community

#### Follow

All Rights Reserved © 2024 Glorious LLC

* Cookie Preferences

USD

{"themeColor":"#4b43ab","iconColor":"#574CD5","showLogo":true,"topBottomPosition":10,"rightLeftPosition":10,"iconSize":"extra-small","iconCustomSize":64,"position":"bottom-left"}
